nicetranslator.com 2017-12-10

# Nice Translator Blog » Nice Translator Privacy Policy

Effective **December 1st, 2008**

### Privacy Notice Table Of Contents

  * Our Commitment To Privacy
  * The Information We Collect
  * How We Use Information
  * Our Commitment To Data Security
  * Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy
  * How To Contact Us

### Our Commitment To Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

### The Information We Collect

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the _NiceTranslator_ website. On some pages, you can make requests and send data. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

  * Name
  * E-Mail Address
  * Content Submission (public comments, etc)

### The Way We Use Information

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive and to privately associate submitted content with its author. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

### Our Commitment To Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

### How To Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at (518) 867-6346 or send us an email at privacy[at]tumbledesign[dot]com.

### Leave a Reply
